<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Congressional App Challenge</string>
    <string name="candidates">Candidates</string>
    <string name="charlie_baker">Charlie Baker</string>
    <string name="karyn_polito">Karyn Polito</string>
    <string name="jay_gonzalez">Jay Gonzalez</string>
    <string name="palfrey">Quentin Palfrey</string>
    <string name="bakerpic">bakerPic</string>
    <string name="bakerprofile1"> \“Since his election as the 72nd Governor of Massachusetts in 2014, Charlie Baker has been committed to delivering bipartisan, commonsense, results-oriented leadership that has made the Commonwealth’s economy, communities, schools and families stronger than ever.\” </string>
    <string name="bakerprofile2"> \"Governor Baker, Lt. Governor Polito and their team on Beacon Hill are working hard to restore taxpayers’ and local leaders’ faith and trust in a government that works harder, smarter and more efficiently to support the people of Massachusetts, holding the line on new taxes and delivering tax relief for working families and small businesses.\" </string>
    <string name="bakerprofile3"> \"Today, the Commonwealth leads the nation in educational achievement, supported by historic investments in public education, local aid, and skill-building to strengthen a highly talented workforce. In Massachusetts, over 150,000 new jobs have been created in the last three years, the number of people working is at an all-time high and incomes are on the rise across the board. Governor Baker has been recognized as a national leader in the battle against the opioid epidemic, with nearly every state in the nation embracing Massachusetts’ landmark approach to increasing substance misuse awareness, education, treatment and prevention.\" </string>
    <string name="bakerprofile4"> \"Raised in Needham, Charlie attended Massachusetts public schools and graduated from Harvard College. He met his wife, Lauren, while earning a Master of Business Administration from the Kellogg Graduate School of Management at Northwestern University.\"</string>
    <string name="bakerprofile5"> \"Lauren Baker has dedicated her tenure as First Lady to her passion for children by expanding the impact of Wonderfund, a nonprofit supporting positive experiences for the Commonwealth’s most vulnerable kids under the care of the state’s Department of Children and Families.\"</string>
    <string name="bakercitation">Information used can be found on the official website of Charlie Baker </string>
    <string name="bakermoreinfo">For more information on Charlie Baker, visit https://www.charliebakerma.com/ </string>
    <string name="voter_registration">Voter Registration</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="politoprofile1"> \"Elected alongside Governor Charlie Baker in 2014, Lieutenant Governor Karyn Polito has championed the Baker-Polito team’s desire to give Massachusetts’ communities a seat at the table on Beacon Hill, building on a fundamental belief and understanding that the Commonwealth’s success is driven by the strength of its 351 cities and towns.\"</string>
    <string name="ltgovernor">Lt. Governor:</string>
    <string name="politoprofile2"> \"Among their first actions in office were releasing $100 million for local transportation infrastructure and establishing a Community Compact Cabinet, chaired by the Lt. Governor, to assist local communities in implementing best-practices that serve constituents more effectively and improve municipal management, reaching agreements in over 300 communities.\" </string>
    <string name="politoprofile3"> \"A longtime advocate for empowering women, Lt. Governor Polito leads the administration’s efforts to support survivors of sexual assault and domestic violence. After years of success in the private sector construction industry, she has also focused on expanding educational opportunity and access to successful careers in science, technology, engineering and math for women and students across the Commonwealth. Karyn’s commitment and dedication to supporting flexible, community-based solutions to growth dates back to her public service as a local selectman in her hometown of Shrewsbury. In 2001, she was elected to the first of five terms in the Massachusetts State House of Representatives serving the residents of the 11th Worcester District, where she championed “Jessica’s Law” toughening mandatory minimum penalties for child sex offenders.\" </string>
    <string name="politoprofile4"> \"Karyn is a lifelong resident of Shrewsbury where her family owns and operates a commercial real estate development firm and where she and her husband, Stephan M. Rodolakis are raising their two children, Bobby and Judy. She is a graduate of Worcester’s Holy Name Central Catholic High School, Boston College and the New England School of Law.\" </string>
    <string name="politomoreinfo"> For more information on Karyn Polito, visit https://www.charliebakerma.com/about-lieutenant-governor-polito </string>
</resources>
